# AMBER OESTREICH

2330 Lexington Ave South, Apt 218 Mendota Heights, MN 55120 United States of America

amber.m.oestreich@gmail.com • +1 651-231-5721 www.amberoestreich.com

## **LEADERSHIP STYLE**

Mix of Autocratic and Participative; strive for perfection in everything and set ambitious goals for self and others

#### **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office
Time Management
Leadership
Problem-Solving
Organization
Critical Thinking
Data Analysis
Adaptability
Positivity

## **BUCKET LIST**

Travel to every continent Become fluent in Spanish

Obtain my MBA

Buy a house

Get married

Design a webpage

Travel to all 50 states

Go Skydiving

Climb a mountain

Make a difference

### **SUMMARY:**

Experienced IKEA co-worker with a strong background in leadership and logistics. Obtained Bachelor's in International Business in May of 2019 and currently working towards Master of Business Administration in a Management concentration with expected graduation of December 2021.

## **EDUCATION:**



#### ST CATHERINE UNIVERSITY

Master of Business Administration, Management September 2019 to Present (Expected December 2021)



#### University of Minnesota—Crookston

Bachelor of Science, International Business August 2012 to May 2019

# **EXPERIENCE:**



#### IKEA—BLOOMINGTON, MN

Preparation & Flow Team Lead (October 2019 to Present)

- Assist in the development of co-workers and peers
- Create schedules to optimize the use of available hours
- Ensure all federal, state, and company regulations are adhered to
- Plan and implement product placement within the warehouse
- Monitor and evaluate assigned space capacities to ensure available stock

Preparation & Flow Co-Worker (August 2017 to October 2019)

- Operate machinery to company and OSHA standards
- Fulfill customer orders
- Plan and implement product locations within warehouse
- Ensure daily load-out is efficiently completed while solving problems that
- Complete aisle maintenance throughout each shift

Self Service Co-Worker (April 2016 to August 2017)

- Prepare space in warehouse for overnight replenishment
- Assist in planning warehouse space for new products
- Assist customers with their shopping needs